Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Collection, Part II: Field Recordings AIA.031.002
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series I: Digitized Tapes, 1965-1997
  - I:A Reference CDs of Digitized Tapes
    - Public Performances, 1965-1997, Jun 25, 1965-Feb 22, 1997
      - Across the Western Ocean – The Story of Irish Traditional Music in America. (folder four) National Public Radio series written, hosted and produced by Mick Moloney. Episodes include: “Did Your Mother Come From Ireland?,” “Happy to Meet, Sorry to Part.” (Two CDs – Total length: 02:02:28) aiamm296C, 297C, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Session in St. Paul, MN. Musicians: Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mick Moloney (mandolin, guitar, vocals), Jack Coen (flute), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Unidentified (concertina, whistle). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:04:37) aiamm230C, Jan 16, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Members of the Chieftains: Sean Potts (whistle), Sean Keane (fiddle) with Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo) and Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle) Informal concert performance at the Cherry Tree, Philadelphia, PA. (One CD – Length: 00:49:32) aiamm217C, Mar 17, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - New York Fleadh Cheoil. Comhaltas Ceoltóirí Éireann Fleadh Cheoil competition and session at Manhattan College, Bronx, NY. Competitors include: John Kennedy, Maureen Dowd, Andrew McDonald, Christopher Ever, John O’Rourke, Edward Boyle, Patricia Conway. Session musicians include: Brendan Mulvihill, Martin Mulvihill, Owen Thomas, Mary O’Callaghan, Keith O’Neill (fiddles), Tom O’Brien (flute), Margie Ford, Marie Tracy, Gail Mulvihill (banjos). (Four CDs – Total length: 01:47:52) aiamm80R, 81R, 82R, 83R, Apr 23, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Leeds Irish Festival. Concert performances and sessions in Leeds, NY. (the Catskills) Musicians include: Billy McComiskey, Richie Dwyer, Patty Moriarty, John Nolan (accordions), Pat Keogh, Johnny Cronin, Andy McGann, Eugene O’Donnell (fiddles), Maureen Doherty (flute), Mick Moloney (guitar, mandolin, banjo, vocals), Emerald Society Pipe Band, Big Wheel Band, Cara Band, Blackwater Boys, Irish Balladeers, Clancy Brothers with Tommy Makem. (Three CDs – 01:49:41) aiamm211C, 212C, Jun 24, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival, Philadelphia, PA. (Folder one) Concert performances by Flying Cloud, Bill Ochs (uilleann pipes, whistle), James Kelly (fiddle), Paddy O’Brien (accordion), Daithi Sproule (guitar, vocals). Evening concert performance by DeDanann: Frankie Gavin (fiddle, whistle), Alec Finn (bouzouki), Jackie Daly (accordion), Johnny “Ringo” McDonagh (bodhran, bones), Tim Lyons (vocals), Charlie Piggott (banjo) (Two CDs – Total length: 01:35:44) aiamm227C, Sep 16, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival, Philadelphia, PA. (Folder two) Fiddle workshop with Tony Demarco, Eugene O’Donnell, James Kelly, Ed Reavy (fiddles). Song and ballad workshop with Fr. Charlie Coen, Richard Hughes, Brian Brooks, Daithi Sproule, Mick Moloney, Tim Lyons and Mike Flynn (vocals). Traditional music played for a ceili by Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle) and Mick Moloney (banjo), Unidentified (whistle). Step dance workshop with music by Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle), Mick Moloney (guitar). Concert performances by Celtic Thunder and DeDanann. (Four CDs – Total length: 03:04:47) aiamm224C, 225C, 226C, Sep 17, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival, Philadelphia, PA. (Folder three) Daytime and evening concert performances by DeDanann: Frankie Gavin (fiddle), Alec Finn (bouzouki), Jackie Daly (accordion), Johnny “Ringo” McDonagh (bodhran, bones), Tim Lyons (vocals), Charlie Piggott (banjo) (Two CDs – Total length: 00:56:28) aiamm 224C, 225C, Sep 17, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Concert at the Cherry Tree: Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle), Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo, mandolin and vocals) Concert performance at the Cherry Tree Folk Co-op, Philadelphia, PA. (Two CDs – Total length 01:11:54) aiamm126R, 314C, Nov, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Moloney, Mick (mandolin, guitar, vocals), O’Donnell, Eugene (fiddle) Concert performance in Philadelphia. (One CD – Length: 00:34:45) aiamm126R, 326R, March 1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Jack Coen (flute, whistle), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina, vocals, whistle), Liz Carroll (fiddle, piano, whistle), Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle) and Bill Ochs (uilleann pipes, whistle). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:01:21) aiamm304R, 305R, May 5, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Washington, D.C. Musicians: Jack Coen (flute, whistle), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina, vocals, whistle), Liz Carroll (fiddle, piano, whistle), Bill Ochs (uilleann pipes, whistle), Donny Golden (dancer), Michael Flatley (dancer, flute). (One CD – Length: 00:32:41) aiamm306R, May 6, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Session at Frank Claudy’s, Washington, D.C. Musicians include: Frank Claudy (flute), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Sean McGlynn (accordion). (One CD – Length: 00:27:55) aiamm261, May 6, 1979-May 7, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Omaha, NE. (Tape indicates last track recorded in Youngstown, OH) Musicians: Jack Coen (flute, whistle), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina, vocals, whistle), Liz Carroll (fiddle, piano, whistle), Bill Ochs (uilleann pipes, whistle), Donny Golden (dancer), Michael Flatley (dancer, flute). (One CD – Length: 00:29:11) aiamm222C, May 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Session at Moloney’s. Musicians: Paddy O’Brien (accordion, b. 1945, Daingean, Co. Offaly), Mike Flynn (vocals, b. Co. Clare), Mick Moloney (banjo), Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle). Traditional music and conversation recorded in Philadelphia, PA. (Four CDs – Total length: 02:39:42) aiamm183C, 272C, Jun 13, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. Evening concert performance in Philadelphia, PA. Musicians include: Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo), Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle), Unidentified (dancers), Larry (L.E.) McCullough (whistle, flute) and Devlish Mary, Richard Hughes (flute), The Flying Cloud: Tony DeMarco (fiddle), Brian Brooks (vocals, mandolin), Caesar Pacifici (guitar). (Four CDs – Total length: 01:35:39) aiamm333C, Sep 17, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Clannad. Concert performance at the International House, Philadelphia, PA. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:29:04) aiamm179C, Nov 4, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Heaney, Joe (sean nos singer). Concert performance at the Denver Folklore Center Concert Hall for the Swallow Hill Music Association, recorded by [?]. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:35:10) aiamm345C, Nov 4, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Seattle, WA. Musicians: Al Purcell (uilleann pipes, whistle), Mike Rafferty (flute), Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin), Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Andy O’Brien (guitar, vocals), Michael Flatley, Donny Golden (dancing). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:35:36) aiamm165C, Nov 11, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Session in Weston, CT. Musicians include: Billy McComiskey, Sean McGlynn (accordions), Mick Moloney (banjo), Andy O’Brien (guitar). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:33:07) aiamm156C, Dec 15, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Session in San Francisco, CA. Musicians: Denis Brooks (uilleann pipes), Richard Twomey (fiddle), Peter Weelan (bouzouki, vocals), Mike Deely (bodhran, bones). (One CD – Length: 00:13:44) aiamm40R, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Session in Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Sean McGlynn (accordion), Jack Coen (flute), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (guitar). (One CD – Length: 00:45:15) aiamm18R, Mar 16,1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Session in Cleveland, OH. Musicians: Tom Byrne (flute), Tom McCaffrey (fiddle), Jimmy Noonan (flute, whistle). (One CD – Length: 00:15:27) aiamm3R, Apr 27, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - O’Donnell, Eugene (fiddle) and Moloney, Mick (banjo, guitar, mandolin, vocals). Concert performance in Nashville, TN. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:26:02) aiamm219C, May 10, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - NAFFM Concert. Musicians: Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals, mandolin), Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle, recitation). Concert performance in Nashville, TN. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:36:23) aiamm313C, Feb 6, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Willie Clancy Summer School Benefit Concert. Musicians: Celtic Thunder, Paddy Reynolds (fiddle), Louise Chalet (guitar), Liam Og O’Flynn (uilleann pipes), Unidentified (accordion, fiddle, piano), Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo), Irish Tradition: Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Andy O’Brien (guitar, vocals), Daithi Sproule (guitar, vocals). Concert performance at George Washington University, Washington, D.C. to benefit the Willie Clancy Summer School. (Four CDs – Total length: 02:31:32) aiamm196C, Apr 10, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Session in Milwaukee, WI. Musicians include: Sean McGlynn, Jackie Daly (accordions), Kevin Burke, Liz Carroll (fiddles), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Mick Moloney (banjo), Micheal O’Domhnaill (guitar). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:04:22) aiamm19R, Aug 1981 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - DeDanann at the Cherry Tree. Concert performance at the Cherry Tree Folk Co-op, Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Frankie Gavin (fiddle, flute), Jackie Daly (accordion), Johnny “Ringo” McDonagh (bodhran, bones), Alec Finn (bouzouki), Maura O’Connell (vocals). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:25:04) aiamm161C, Oct 1981 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Concert in Geneva, NY. Musicians: Sean McGlynn (accordion, whistle), Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle), Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals), Steve Gallagher, Laura Kelly (dancers). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:35:00) aiamm310C, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Various Artists and Sessions. (Tape marked “E O’Donnell - Tunes”) Recorded in [Philadelphia, PA?] Musicians include: Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle), Unidentified (accordion, uilleann pipes, fiddle). (One CD – Length: 00:22:45) aiamm221C, Feb, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - St. Patrick’s Celebration: Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, mandolin, vocals), Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle), Donny Golden (dancing), Blended Scotch: Jimmy Kelly (guitar, vocals) Unidentified (vocals, whistle). Concert performance in Nashville, TN. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:25:39) aiamm192C, Mar 12, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Harte, Frank (vocals, song collector, b. May 14, 1933, Chapelizod, Co. Dublin, d. June 27, 2005), Moloney, Mick (banjo, mandolin) Concert performance at Godfrey Daniels, Bethlehem, PA. (Three CDs – Total length: 01:59:55) aiamm279C, 341C, Jun 18, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Concert at the Eagle Tavern: Robbie O’Connell (vocals, guitar), James Keane (button accordion, concertina), Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo, mandolin, vocals) Concert performance at the Eagle Tavern, W.14th St., New York, NY. (Two CDs – Total length 01:35:02) aiamm10R, Jun 30, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Carroll, Liz (fiddle), McGreevy, John (fiddle, b.1919, Chicago, IL), Keane, Jimmy (piano accordion) Concert performance in Knoxville, TN at the World’s Fair. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:25:22) aiamm141R, Jul, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Moloney, Mick, and the Irish Tradition: Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, mandolin, vocals), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Andy O’Brien (guitar, vocals). Concert performance at the World’s Fair, Knoxville TN. (One CD – Length: 00:36:08) aiamm190C, Jul, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Session in Milwaukee, WI. Musicians: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Mick Moloney (guitar, mandolin). (One CD – Length: 00:49:09) aiamm20R, Aug, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Milwaukee, WI. Musicians: Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo, mandolin, vocals), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina, vocals), Donny and Eileen Golden (dancers), Timmy Britton (uilleann pipes, whistle), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle) (One CD – Length: 00:40:27) aiamm223C, Aug 21, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. Session and concert performance recorded in Lansdowne, PA. Musicians include: Martin Mulhaire (accordion), Jack Coen, Mike Rafferty, Seamus Egan (flutes), Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle), Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals). (One CD – Length: 00:27:15) aiamm137R, circa 1982 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - "Music of Mick Moloney" (Mick Moloney and various artists) Radio broadcast on Boston’s WERS, Folk Music of Ireland and the British Isles hosted by Brian O’Donovan featuring a retrospective of Moloney’s recordings. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:36:18) aiamm186C, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - O’Connell, Robbie (guitar, vocals), Keane, James (button accordion, concertina), Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals, mandolin, banjo) at Godfrey Daniels. Concert performance at Godfrey Daniels in Bethlehem, PA. (Three CDs – Total length: 02:19:19) aiamm163C, 164C, Feb 17, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Smithsonian Concert. Concert performance at the Smithsonian Institute, Washington, D.C. Musicians: Mick Moloney (banjo, vocals, mandolin), Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals), James Keane (accordion, concertina), Jerry O’Sullivan (uilleann pipes, whistle), Johnny McGreevy (fiddle), Joe Shannon (uilleann pipes). (One CD – Length: 00:51:26) aiamm229C, Jul, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Augusta Heritage Center. Concert performance at Davis and Elkins College, Elkins, West Virginia. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, mandolin, vocals), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Donny Golden (dancer), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes, whistle, flute). (One CD – Length: 01:01:20) aiamm331C, Jul 12, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Augusta Heritage Center. Concert performance at Davis and Elkins College, Elkins, West Virginia. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, mandolin, vocals), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Donny Golden (dancer), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes, whistle, flute). (One CD – Length: 01:00:43) aiamm332C, Jul 14, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Concert at the Eagle Tavern: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (guitar and vocals) Concert performance at the Eagle Tavern, W.14th St., New York, NY. (Two CDs – Total length 01:33:18) aiamm16R, Aug 27, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Festival of Traditional American Dance. Concert performance at the Hotel Ivoire, Abidjan, Cote d’Ivoire, Africa. Performers include: Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Donny and Eileen Golden (dancing). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:26:38) aiamm270C, 271C, Sep 28, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - O’Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Unidentified (harp), O’Sullivan, Jerry (uilleann pipes), Moloney, Mick (guitar). O’Donnell plays in a studio (slow air), on a WHYY broadcast (slow air), and in concert [original cassette labeled “Hornpipes (Own & Liz’)]. (One CD – Length: 00:15:58) aiamm318C, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Moloney, Mick (banjo, mandolin, vocals), Keane, Jimmy (piano accordion), O’Connell, Robbie (guitar, vocals). Concert performance and brief interview at the University of Arizona, Tucson, AZ., broadcast on KVAT – FM (NPR). (Three CDs – Total length: 01:38:59) aiamm281C, 282C, Feb 5,1984 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Session 1984. [Philadelphia, PA?] Musicians include: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Jimmy Keane (piano accordion), Seamus Egan (banjo), Mick Moloney (mandolin). (One CD – Length: 00:48:08) aiamm215C, Mar, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Sessions with Seamus Egan (flute, banjo) Traditional music recorded in Miltown Malbay, Co. Clare. (One CD – Length: 00:58:38) aiamm184C, Jul, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Sessions with Seamus Egan (flute, banjo) Traditional music recorded in Ollie Conway’s and Wilson’s in Miltown Malbay, Co. Clare. (One CD – Length: 00:42:56) aiamm187C, Jul, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Augusta Heritage Center. Concert performance at Davis and Elkins College, Elkins, West Virginia. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, mandolin, vocals), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Donny Golden (dancer), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes, whistle, flute), Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals), Frank Harte (vocals). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:04:14) aiamm334C, Jul, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Augusta Heritage Center. Concert performance at Davis and Elkins College, Elkins, West Virginia. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, mandolin, vocals), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Donny Golden (dancer), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes, whistle, flute), Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals), Frank Harte (vocals). (One CD – Length: 00:59:05) aiamm335C, Jul, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Scottsdale, AZ. Musicians: Jerry O’Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (flute, whistle, concertina), Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (button accordion), Donny Golden (dancing), Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals). (Four CDs – Total length: 02:09:25) aiamm167C, 168C, Oct 28, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in New Orleans, LA. Musicians: Jerry O’Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (flute, whistle, concertina), Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (button accordion), Donny Golden (dancing), Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals). (Three CDs – Total length: 01:59:07) aiamm169C, 170C, Nov 2, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Memphis, TN. Musicians: Jerry O’Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (flute, whistle, concertina), Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (button accordion), Donny Golden (dancing), Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals). (One CD – Length: 00:44:57) aiamm136R, Nov 3, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Folk Music with Gene Shay. Radio program recorded by Gene Shay and broadcast on either WXPN-FM or WHYY-FM in Philadelphia, PA. Traditional music and interview with Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin, guitar, vocals), Eugene O’Donnell (fiddle), Seamus Egan (flute), Jerry O’Sullivan (uilleann pipes). (One CD – Length: 00:18:16) aiamm274C, Mar, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance. Concert performance at the ruins of the Grand Hotel (Casa Grande) in Managua, Nicaragua. Susie Goff and the Green Grass Cloggers, Mick Moloney (mandolin) and Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals) perform as part of the South American tour of Irish and Appalachian musicians for the United States Information Agency. (One CD – Length: 00:41:50) aiamm202C, May 4, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance. Concert performance at the ruins of the Grand Hotel (Casa Grande) in Managua, Nicaragua. Susie Goff and the Green Grass Cloggers, Mick Moloney (mandolin) and Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals) perform as part of the South American tour of Irish and Appalachian musicians for the United States Information Agency. (One CD – Length: 00:51:34) aiamm203C, May 5, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance. Concert performance at the ruins of the Grand Hotel (Casa Grande) in Managua, Nicaragua. Susie Goff and the Green Grass Cloggers, Mick Moloney (mandolin) and Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals) perform as part of the South American tour of Irish and Appalachian musicians for the United States Information Agency. (One CD – Length: 00:51:06) aiamm204C, May 6, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance. Concert performance at the ruins of the Grand Hotel (Casa Grande) in Managua, Nicaragua. Susie Goff and the Green Grass Cloggers, Mick Moloney (mandolin) and Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals) perform as part of the South American tour of Irish and Appalachian musicians for the United States Information Agency. (One CD – Length: 00:40:07) aiamm205C, May 7, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Milwaukee, WI. Musicians: Timmy Britton (uilleann pipes), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina, flute), Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (button accordion), Donny and Eileen Golden (dancing), Robbie O’Connell (guitar, vocals), Jimmy Keane (piano accordion), James Keane, Sr. (sean nos singer). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:17:26) aiamm135R, Aug, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Moloney, Mick (banjo, mandolin, vocals), Keane, Jimmy (piano accordion), O’Connell, Robbie (guitar, vocals), Carroll, Liz (fiddle), Bernstein, Ira (dancing). Concert performance at the Wheatland Music Festival, Remus, MI. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:32:10) aiamm298C, Sep, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals, banjo), Keane, James (accordion), Egan, Seamus (mandolin, flute, mandolin) Concert performance in Bethlehem, PA. (probably at Godfrey Daniels). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:31:48) aiamm284C, Dec 28, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals, mandolin, banjo), Keane, James (accordion), Egan, Seamus (mandolin, flute, whistle, uilleann pipes, banjo). Concert performance at the Turning Point, Piermont, NY. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:25:43) aiamm278C, Mar 1, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Moloney, Mick (banjo, mandolin, vocals), Keane, Jimmy (piano accordion), O’Connell, Robbie (guitar, vocals). Concert performance at the Cuyahoga Valley Festival in the Cuyahoga Valley National Recreation Area near Cleveland, OH. recorded by WKSU – FM. (One CD – Length: 00:41:29) aiamm330C, Sep 19, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Cherish the Ladies. Concert performance in Geneva, NY. Musicians: Joanie Madden (flute, whistle), Mary Coogan (guitar), Maureen Doherty (flute, accordion, whistle), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Siobhan Egan (fiddle, whistle), Bridget Fitzgerald (vocals), Eileen Golden, Mairead Powell, Maureen Kennelly (dancers). (Three CDs – Total Length: 01:41:05) aiamm206, 207C, Oct 10, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Cherish the Ladies. Concert performance at Brookdale Community College in Lincroft, NJ. Musicians: Joanie Madden (flute, whistle), Mary Coogan (guitar), Maureen Doherty (flute, accordion, whistle), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Siobhan Egan (fiddle, whistle), Bridget Fitzgerald (sean nos singer), Eileen Golden, Mairead Powell, Maureen Kennelly (dancers) and Cathie [Ryan] Henry (vocals) in her first appearance with the group. (Three CDs – Total Length: 01:48:24 ) aiamm208C, 209C, Mar 20, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Cherish the Ladies. Concert performance in Woodside, Queens, NY. Musicians: Joanie Madden (flute, whistle), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Eileen Golden, Mairead Powell, Maureen Kennelly (dancers), Siobhan Egan (fiddle), Maureen Doherty (accordion, flute), Mary Coogan (guitar), Cathie Ryan, Bridget Fitzgerald (vocals). (Three CDs – Total length: 01:46:10) aiamm275C, 276C, Apr 30, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Ceili with Maureen Glynn. Called by Kevin Westley and Maureen Kennelly. Musicians: Maureen Glynn (fiddle), Buddy Connolly (accordion), Pete Mancuso (guitar, banjo). (One CD – Length: 00:53:20) aiamm276C, circa 1988 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - O’Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Moloney, Mick (banjo, guitar, vocals, mandolin). Concert performance at the Cuyahoga Valley National Recreation Area, near Cleveland, OH. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:23:14) aiamm315C, Sep 16, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 22)